你自个住得咋样
So, how's living alone?
你懂得 很有意思
You know, it's interesting.
刚刚搬进新公寓的时候
When I first moved into my new apartment,
我有点紧张
I was nervous.
人生中第一次没有了室友
For the first time in my adult life, I didn't have a roommate.
但是 哥突然醒悟了
But then it hit me:
哥人生中第一次木有室友呢
for the first time in my adult life, I didn't have a roommate!
要是哥想裸着 没人管呀
If I want to walk around naked, nobody cares.
要是哥想把洗衣篮放在客厅里
If I want to leave the laundry basket
没人在乎呀
in the middle of the living room, nobody stops me.
要是哥买的点汤在冰箱里放两天
If I bring home soup from the deli
没人抢呀
and leave it in the fridge for two days, nobody eats it.
要是哥做了什么傻了吧唧的事儿
And if I do something colossally stupid,
没人知道呀
nobody ever has to know.
人们总是爱嘲笑那些
People make fun of the guy
整晚呆在家无所事事的人
who stays home every night doing nothing.
但事实上 那些人是天才
But the truth is... that guy's a genius.
老实说 一个人看着电视
Because let's be honest, sitting around watching TV,
喝着小酒 吃着炸排骨
drinking beer and eating ribs alone is what every
简直就是每个美国公民都渴望的生活
red-blooded American would rather be doing at all times.
但是有人和你一起分享不是更好吗
Yeah, but wouldn't it be better to have someone to share the...
我是说 你不会觉得有点孤独么
I mean, don't you get lonely without...
好吧 听起来确实很爽
Yeah, that sounds pretty great.
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第二十一集
翻译:  园丁姐姐 数字哥 47.4 Roy 加菲猪
后期+统筹: Cathy Roy 校对: Andie
Ivy, let's work together, our year will be legend---wait for it---dary!
HIMYM字幕组倾情奉献
你是不是在问
What's the best thing
和脱衣舞女郎谈恋爱的最大好处是什么
about dating a stripper, you ask?
木有
Nope.
她只是问你要喝点什么
Just asked for your drink order.
哥来告诉你 最棒的是啥
I'll tell you the best thing about dating a stripper.
给他杯威士忌
He'll just have a scotch.
我就可以说
Getting to say,
嘿 哥找了个脱衣舞女郎
"Hey, I'm dating a stripper."
我得走了
And I should go.
我得去赚面包钱了
Time to make the doughnuts.
确切地说 是坐在蛋蛋上赚面包钱哦
More like time to make some dough sitting on some nuts.
她是个脱衣舞女郎哟
She's a stripper.
哥跟她在恋爱哟
I'm dating her.
哥跟个脱衣舞女郎恋爱哟 哥是人生赢家
I'm dating a stripper. Barney wins.
我送你出去
I'll walk you out.
嘿 去哪呢
Hey, where are you going?
奎恩得去上班了 她是个
Quinn needs to get to work. She's a...
我懂得 脱衣舞女郎
I know, a stripper, got it.
嘿 出租车
Hey, taxi!
我女朋友是个脱衣舞女郎
My girlfriend's a stripper!
泰德 知道我们周五晚上要去哪里吃大餐么
So, Ted, guess where we're having dinner Friday night.
银色法式餐厅
Chez L'Argent.
姐好鸡冻哟
I am so excited.
我们折腾了很久才预定到位子
We've been trying forever to get this reservation.
能等等么
Can you hold on for just one second?
你丫在搞毛啊
What the hell are you doing?
没有啊
Nothing.
你不是说你想去尿尿么
Did you say you had to pee?
没有
No.
好吧 姐得去尿尿了
But yeah, I do have to pee.
靠 这小屁孩最好给老娘长得可爱点
Man, this kid better be real freakin' cute!
怎么了
What was that all about?
莉莉昨晚上做了个春梦
Lily had a sex dream last night.
春梦吗 给哥说说
Sex dream? Do tell.
我正在给宝宝用的家具上漆
I was painting the baby furniture...
噢耶
Oh, yeah.
快点啊 马修快回家了
Hurry up, before Marshall gets home.
噢
Oh, oh...
哇唔
Whoa!
宝贝 真抱歉
I'm sorry, baby.
你睡着了吗
Were you asleep?
所有怀孕的女人都会做疯狂的春梦
All pregnant ladies have crazy sex dreams.
那只是荷尔蒙作祟啦
It's just her hormones going berserk.
那这次谁是她的春梦对象呢
So who's responsible for her rapid thigh movement this time?
我喜欢那个她上了乔治・华盛顿的梦
Oh, my favorite was when she banged George Washington.
我更喜欢那个她和比尔・考斯比
I liked the three-way with
还有蓝爸爸一起玩双飞的梦
Bill Cosby and Papa Smurf.
噢 蓝爸爸把她咔咔得都咔咔了
Oh, he smurfed the smurf out of her.
对啊 考斯比只好一个人默默在角落咔咔咔
Yes, while The Cos smurfed off in the corner.
我们都记得这个梦 说正事
We all remember. But here's the thing.
当莉莉做春梦的时候
When Lily has dirty dreams about other people,
她都会告诉我她的春梦对象
she always tells me.
但是这次
But this time...
听起来好像你做了个怪梦
Sounds like you had a crazy dream.
梦见啥了
What was it about?
然后她的脸变成了
And then her face turned...
朱砂红
vermilion.
就是 你和我
Just... you and me...
滚床单啦 一对一
gettin' it on, monogamously.
爽歪歪了
Monoga-me-oh-my.
不是小尴尬时的那种玫瑰红
Not the rose quartz of the slightly embarrassed,
也不是有点窘时的那种番茄红
or the tomato red of the mildly abashed,
而是朱砂红 那种淫荡的羞愧色
vermilion, the color of carnal shame.
这就意味着一件事
Can only mean one thing:
莉莉在梦里上了一个我们都认识的人
Lily dream-banged someone we know.
好吧 你真相了
Okay, you caught me vermilion-handed.
哥花了五年的时间
The truth is, I've spent the last five years
inception暗指盗梦空间
试图进到你媳妇的梦中
trying to inception your wife.
那部电影是两年前出的呀
That movie only came out two years ago.
什么电影
What movie?
你知道哥猜是谁吗
You know who I bet it is?
罗宾
Robin.
不是她 哥证实过了
Already checked.
莉莉和我去
Lily and I paid her a visit
环球新闻台总部找过她一次
at the new World Wide News headquarters.
我太激动了  因为我花了好几个月
And I'm so excited, because I've been trying months
才订到这个餐厅的位子
to get this reservation.
不好意思耽搁一秒钟
Can you hold on just one second?
你到底想干什么
What the hell are you doing?!
啥也没干啊
Nothing.
照片很棒    哦
Nice photo. Oh.
你的护照应该超级大吧
Your passport must be enormous.
啊呵呵
Ugh.
这个吧 老实说 我不想要这东西
You know, for the record, I didn't want this.
本意不想要 有了也不认可哦
Didn't want it, did not approve it.
简直太让人难堪了嘛
It's super embarrassing.
嘿   莫尔
Hey, merle
哦   对了  你们想去看看我的办公桌吗
So, uh, do you guys want to come up and see my desk?
当然   干嘛不
Yeah, why not?
来
Come on.
证件
I.D.?
哦    嗯    那个就是我
Oh. Um, that is me.
女士    恕我冒昧
Ma'am, with all due respect,
你比那个辣妹要老上那么一点点
you're a wee bit older than that hottie.
我的老天哪
For God sakes.
你瞧瞧  我每天都在国家电视台亮相
You know, here I am, on national TV every day,
结果一个在我巨幅照旁边坐了一辈子的人
and still a guy who spends his whole life sitting next to
居然不知道我是谁
a giant picture of me has no idea who I am.
我才没有在这里坐一辈子  我可是玩乐队的
This isn't my whole life; I'm in a band.
而且我们会飞黄腾达的
And we're gonna make it.
孩子们   他们确实飞黄腾达了
And, kids, they did make it.
那件事我以后再细说
But I'll get to that later.
那个其实吧   我以后很可能不会细说
You know what, I'm probably not going to get to that later.
他们出过一曲  不算太逊  仅此而已
They had one song, it didn't suck, the end.
你不是总说出不出名并不重要
You always said it wasn't about being famous.
你只是想踏踏实实做新闻   对吗
You just want to do solid journalism, right?
没错   嗯
Yeah, well...
我当然想出名啦
Of course I want to be famous!
在加拿大   我可是罗宾亮晶晶
In Canada, I was Robin Sparkles.
我的名字家喻屋晓（加拿大人多住木屋）
I was a cabinhold name.
可在这儿
But here?
不用看你证件   莫尔
Don't need to see your I.D., Merle.
所有人都认识你
Everyone knows who you are.
你是莫尔
You're Merle.
他只在圣诞派对的滑稽短剧里出现过一次
He was in one skit in the Christmas party!
哦   对了   泰德最近怎么样
Uh, by the way, how is Ted doing?
孩子们    你们还记的发生了什么事吗
Kids, you remember what happened.
我向她表白    被她拒绝
I declared my love, she turned me down,
我们都搬出了公寓    现在
we both moved out of the apartment, and now...
我好久没和他说话了  自从我们  没再说话了
I haven't talked to him since we... stopped talking.
他过的不错
He's pretty good.
不错
Pretty good?
昨天晚上 你只穿着白色小内内
Last night, you ate a box of Froot Loops
吃光了一盒麦片
in your tighty whities.
不对  我神马都没穿
No, I demolished a box of Froot Loops,
狂吞了一盒之麦片
fully nude.
对    是还"不错"
Yeah, "Pretty good" Works.
嗨    巴尼
Hey, Barney.
嗨    莉莉
Hey, Lily.
你知道这是怎么回事吗
Do you know what this is about?
啊哈
Uh-huh.
我需要知道吗
Do I want to know?
不好意思    不是你   哥们
No, sorry, bro.
大爷的
Damn it!
好    该我的事迹了
Okay, time for my stuff.
哥几个    昨晚上我坐在家里
Guys, I was sitting at home last night,
忽然间    我感到了醒湖灌顶
and all of a sudden, I had a piphany.
我的醒湖灌顶就是这个
And my piphany was this...
实际上  那个  那个应该叫"醍醐灌顶"
Actually, it's, uh, it's "Epiphany."
错  泰德 你是醍醐   我是醒湖
No, Ted, this is the piphany.
我这就说出来了
And here it is:
让  每个  夜晚  成为传奇
Make... every... night... legendary.
哥几个    我们有过
Guys, we've had
一些相当传奇的夜晚
some pretty legendary nights.
但是我们也曾有过一些不那么传奇的夜晚
But we've also had some nights that weren't so legendary.
比如泰德逼大家去看"我老婆是巨无霸"的那天
Lookin' at you, The Night Ted Made Us All Watch Norbit.
艾迪・墨菲演的肥妻    这还有问题啊
Eddie Murphy as a fat lady; what's the problem?
那个是艾迪 墨菲演的
That was Eddie Murphy?
不传奇的夜晚从此不再
The non-legendary nights are done.
从现在开始    我们今后每一个夜晚
From here on in, every single night of our lives
都会成为永生难忘的夜晚
will be a night we'll never forget.
从今夜开始
Starting tonight.
迄今最悠久疯狂的历险 谁准备好了
Who's ready for the longest, craziest adventure yet?!
很好
Good.
我们团队中的弱者已经被淘汰了
The weak have been weeded from our herd.
你准备好去狂欢了吗    泰德
You ready to rock and roll, Ted?
那个    我也要回家了
Yeah, I'm going home, too.
我预感到可能要出什么奇装异服的幺蛾子
I'm sensing some costumes coming up here
我还是眼不见为净
and I'd rather steer clear.
泰德    20年以后
Ted, 20 years from now,
当你是个老光棍而我是美国总统的时候
when you're all alone and I'm President,
你的回忆的内容不应该是
you're not gonna remember
泡在公寓里无所事事
sitting around your apartment doing nothing.
你将会回想起这个夜晚
What you will remember is that tonight,
今夜
this night...
是我们组建墨西哥街头乐队之夜！
was The Night We Started a Mariachi Band!
一    二    三    四
Uno, dos, tres, quatro!
好吧    你是对的
Okay, you were right.
难忘之夜
Memorable night.
这个和明晚相比微不足道啊    兄弟
That was nothing compared to ma?ana, amigo.
因为明晚将会成为
Because ma?ana is gonna be...
吃遍菜单之夜
The Night We Ate Everything on the Menu!
真是个难忘之夜
A really memorable night.
但是明天晚上
But tomorrow night...
是牵马进酒吧之夜
Is The Night We Brought a Horse into the Bar!
好吧 但是明天...
Okay, but tomorrow...
明天晚上 是自由女神像蹦极之夜
Is The Night We Bungee Jump off the Statue of Liberty!
没门儿
Nope.
这个晚上是你们的莉莉阿姨和马修叔叔
That night was the night of Aunt Lily
的浪漫晚餐之夜
and Uncle Marshall's fancy dinner.
外加上浪漫的豪华车接送
Complete with a fancy limo ride.
惊喜哦
Surprise!
嗨
Hello!
嗨 兰吉
Hi, Ranjit.
不是吧
No.
要不要我从城西干道走呢
Should I take the West Side Highway?
为什么不呢 兰吉
Why not, Ranjit?
你不总是想怎样就怎样么
Don't you always just take whatever you want,
为了满足你那些个肮脏 变态 扭曲
regardless of anything but your own
的欲望可以不顾一切
dirty, sick, twisted appetites?
我还是继续走百老汇吧
I'll stay on Broadway.
证件
I.D.?
老天呐 睁开你的狗...
For God's sakes, open your...
哦 好吧
Yeah, that's about right.
证件
I.D.?
罗宾终于认识到
Robin had finally learned the lesson
没有人可以一夜成名
that nobody gets famous overnight.
巧合的是
But here's the crazy part:
就在那个晚上 她的名字家喻户晓了
that night, she got famous.
罗宾 你在这儿啊
Robin, there you are.
桑迪?里弗斯
Sandy Rivers!
节目之星啊
Star of the show.
还好啦 哥们儿
What it is, my man. Yeah.
罗宾 我有件大事儿交给你
Robin, I've got something big for you,
很"大"的事儿哦
something huge.
交到你身"上"了
And I want you on it.
桑迪 之前你可是在骚扰视频"里"面
Sandy, you were in the harassment video.
顺便说一句 你表现很棒哦
You were great in that, by the way.
谢啦 伙计
Thanks, holmes.
我很欣赏你那个肮脏的小心眼儿
And I like the way
但是 罗宾 这可是真事儿
your filthy little mind works, Robin, but this is real.
爆炸性事件
Big story's breaking.
你害怕直升机么
Are you afraid of helicopters?
我爱死直升机了
I love helicopters.
-要我去直播什么 战争   -比战争更好
-What am I covering, a war?   -Better!
环球新闻带你走遍世界
World Wide News brings you the world.
现在由罗宾为你带来交通实况
And now Robin Scherbatsky with traffic.
如果你不想去蹦极 没关系
You don't want to go bungee jumping, fine.
今晚 我们将去国家自然历史博物馆
Tonight's The Night We Stole a Mummy
偷一具木乃伊出来
from the Natural History Museum!
哦 我才不干
Yeah, I'm not doing that.
那你可以带上你的地铁卡 泰德 今晚
Then get out your MetroCard, Ted, because tonight's
我们要去地下和那些流浪汉们开个派对
The Night We Partied with the Mole People!
巴尼 我的冰箱里有一人份的斯托弗宽面条
Barney, I have a Stouffer's lasagna for one in the freezer
那将会是十分难忘的
that is going to be unforgettable.
我的录像机里存了足够我看到进棺材的
I have a Sanford and Son on my DVR
《桑福德和儿子》
that I will take with me to my grave.
我不需要做别的事儿来让今晚永生难忘了
I don't need tonight to be any more memorable than that.
好吧 《桑福德和儿子》听起来是不错
Okay, Sanford and Son does sound good.
但是 如果要我提一个反对的理由的话
But if I could just present a counter argument...
你被锁在门外啦 傻瓜
You're locked out, dummy!
擦嘞 巴尼
Damn it! Barney!
手机给我 我要打给公寓管理员
Give me your phone; I'm calling my super.
今晚我们会打给每一个我们认识的人
The only person we're calling is everyone we know,
因为今晚我们将会跟踪菲尔?科林斯
because tonight's The Night We Tracked Down Phil Collins,
和他成为哥们儿 劝他和彼得・盖布瑞尔重组乐队
Became Best Friends with Him, and Talked Him into Reuniting
然后我们就能成为他们新专辑的和声歌手
with Peter Gabriel, So Then We Got to Sing Backup
那是一件多赞的事情啊
On The New Genesis Album and It Was Awesome!
好吧 我去用酒吧的电话
Fine, I'll use the phone at the bar.
兰吉 你能关上隔离板么
Ranjit, would you please put up the partition?
关上隔离板
Partition going up.
你居然在梦里意淫了兰吉
You had a sex dream about Ranjit!
嘿
Hello.
兰吉
Ranjit!
不好意思
Sorry.
好吧 是的 我是这么做了
Okay, yes, I did,
但这不能说明任何事
but it didn't mean anything.
好的 很好 那个梦里你梦到了什么
Okay, well, what happened in this dream?
我想知道一切
And I want to know everything.
一切的细节
Every explicit detail.
别遗漏哪怕一点点
Don't leave out any...
擦嘞 兰吉
Damn it, Ranjit!
不好意思
Sorry.
马修 那只是一个梦
Marshall, it was a dream.
哦 是么
Yeah, well, dreams are just stuff
梦是心头想
that you subconsciously want to happen.
要不然你认为我怎么会梦到
Why do you think I'm constantly dreaming
大脚怪在维京队打四分卫
about Bigfoot playing quarterback for the Vikings?
因为你是看着那幅画睡着的
Because you fall asleep looking at a painting of it.
那幅画能让我放松
It soothes me.
别转移话题
Don't try to change the subject.
你在梦里出轨
You sleep-cheated.
你在梦里到处和人睡
You've been sleep-sleeping around,
我难以接受啊
and I'm sick of it.
你知道么 我现在有直接下车
You know, I have half a mind
让你一个人去吃那该死的晚餐的念头
to get out and let you eat all by yourself.
我该靠边停车么
Should I pull over?
擦嘞 兰吉
Damn it, Ranjit!
是的 兰吉  靠边停了吧
Yes, Ranjit. Pull over.
靠边停车
Pulling over.
看着 泰德
You watch, Ted.
今晚将会是传奇--
Tonight is going to be legen--
我们今晚会去偷一头骆驼
it's the night we stole a camel...
这意味着今晚将会充满戏剧--性的
...which means it'll be full of drama-- dary.
和前面"戏剧性"的谐音
充满了单峰骆驼
Dromedary!
我为你神一般的造词能力鼓掌
I applaud your wordplay
但是你把前提搞错了
but your core premise is flawed.
夜夜传奇是不可能的
Every night can't be legendary.
如果每个晚上都如此传奇 那么就没有传奇之夜了
If all nights are legendary, no nights are legendary.
泰德 你看你摆得什么态度
See, Ted, that attitude right there,
那就是为何我领先于你
that's why I'm in the lead.
你的领先什么意思
What do you mean, in the lead?
我说的是游戏人生啊 泰德童鞋
I'm talking about the game of life, Ted.
计分板
Scoreboard.
更好的衣装75点
Better wardrobe: 75 points.
公寓的楼层比你高 90点
Apartment on a higher floor: 90 points.
名字比你长一点 110点
Longer name: 110 points.
插一句 这套点数规则是你定的吗
Sorry. Did you just make up this point system?
制定点数规则 114点
Made up the point system: 114 points.
既然你指出这一点 就赏你10点好了
And ten points to you for pointing that out.
不错哟 泰德
Nice job, Ted.
足够大方到会赏你这10点
15 points to me for being gracious enough
就给自己个15点好了
to give you those ten points.
但是有一点 泰德
But here's the point, Ted.
每次我出去逍遥
Every time I go out
缔造传奇夜晚
and have an awesome night
而且你却没来
and you're not there,
我这栏里又多了100点的说
that's another 100 points in my column.
于是乎我领先了
So yeah, I'm in the lead.
巴尼 回家过夜这一事实
Barney, the fact that I can stay home for a night
证明我内心平和
shows that I have inner peace
而且我觉得没必要去争这个点那个点的
and that I don't feel the need to keep score.
这就差不多值个1000点了吧
That's worth like 1,000 points right there,
所以说句良心话 我们打平
so at the very least, we're tied.
我们才不是平手好伐
We're so not tied.
Tie既有打平又有系紧的意思
尽管你知道什么东西是系紧的
Although you know what is tied--
我女朋友的比基尼上的衣带
the strap of my girlfriend's bikini.
但有时是松的 因为她是脱衣舞娘
Except when it's not, 'cause she's a stripper.
一百万点 游戏结束
One million points! Game.
嘘
Shh.
结束了
It's over.
都过去了 过去了
It's done. It's done.
喂 你是做什么的
So what do you do?
你开玩笑的对吧
You're kidding, right?
我是前方记者
I... I'm an on-air reporter.
我五分钟前才做过一篇报道
I just did a report like five minutes ago.
你听起来很挫败啊
You sound frustrated.
没错
Yeah, I am.
我累死累活 而且和以前一样 没人把我当回事
I'm busting my ass, and as usual, no recognition.
罗宾 我干这行也有段时间了
Robin, I've been doing this a while,
如果有什么东西我学到的 就是咕噜
and if there's one thing I've learned, it's flarm.
什么咕噜
What? Flarm.
咕噜咕噜咕噜
Flarm, flarm, flarm.
叽里呱啦
Blobbum.
你出啥毛病了
What is wrong with you?
你中风了还是什么
Are you having a stroke?
事实上 他就是中风了
As a matter of fact, he was.
喂 挺住啊 等会儿
Oh! Hold on! Wait!
与此同时 莉莉非常
Meanwhile, Lily was in
急切的需要一位女性朋友
desperate need of a female friend.
莉莉 这我都见了无数遍了
Lily, I have seen this a million times.
孩子要出生了 男人都会不正常的
Guys go crazy when there's a baby on the way.
你应该知道我们经理在他老婆怀孕时的样子吧
You should have seen the manager when his wife got pregnant.
怀孕七个月时 他就不让她继续当脱衣舞娘了
After the second trimester, he made her stop stripping.
嗯 你说的很对
Yeah, you're right.
我觉得很愧疚
Now I feel bad.
我们的晚餐一定是毁了
Our big dinner's been ruined.
马修现在多半在哭呢
Marshall's probably crying right now.
我不知道这里的食物会如此美味
I had no idea that food could be this delicious.
马修 你现在很不正常
Marshall, you are being crazy.
没有没有 我搞的定
No, no, I can handle it.
如果我把我的本本卖了
If I sell my laptop,
我们可以再吃一次这些南瓜花
we can get seconds on those squash blossoms.
我说的是莉莉
I mean about Lily.
嗯 你知道的 她现在也不正常
Well, you know, she's being crazy, too.
她怀孕了
She's pregnant.
她就应该不正常
She gets to be crazy.
而你应该是正常的那个
You have to be the sane one.
怎么 在孩子出生之前我再也不能
So what, I don't get to be crazy again
表现得不正常了吗
until the baby comes?
当然不能 接下来就该轮到小宝宝不正常了
No. Then it's baby's turn to be crazy.
那我什么时候可以再不正常一下
When do I get to be crazy again?
不可能了
Never.
少年狂笑中
我们完全打平了
We are totally even.
我们绝对不是平手 原因如下
We absolutely are not even, and here's why.
就算加上你
I'll grant you that if you include
设计摩天楼的12分
the 12 points for designing the skyscraper,
和汤米・李击掌的83分
the 83 points for slapping five with Tommy Lee
还有比我先泡到罗宾的9000分
and the 9,000 points for banging Robin before me,
我们也才刚好并驾齐驱
our point totals would be about neck and neck,
但是有件事情你忘记了
but there's one thing you're forgetting.
我不在乎的这个事实
The fact that I don't care?
不
No.
而且你因为顶嘴再扣掉5点
And you just lost five points for sass.
你记得我们三年前的一段对话吗
Do you remember a conversation we had about three years ago?
巴尼 你是王
Barney, you're the king.
没有人可以做到像你一样泡到妞
Nobody picks up chicks like you.
你真是 英俊
You're handsome,
令人愉悦
debonair,
一切我希望成为的东西
everything I wish I could be.
我怎么觉得这事儿从来没有发生过
I'm starting to think this never happened.
让你自己说完
Let you finish.
你舌灿莲花 魅力四射
You're smooth, charismatic,
温伦尔雅
"Sauve."
你是说温文尔雅吧
I think you mean "Suave."
啊哈
Aha.
这么说你确实记得
So you do remember.
但是有一件事
But there's one thing
即便是像你一样的泡妞大神也是做不了的
even a master ladies' man like you could never do,
如果你能做的话
and if you could ever do it,
这件事值500点
it would be worth 500 points.
你勾起我的兴趣了 比我矮一点的小朋友
You have my attention, my slightly shorter friend.
挑战如下
Here's the challenge.
穿着裙子要来一个女孩子的电话号码
Get a girl's phone number while you're wearing a dress.
挑战...
Challenge...
完成
Accomplished.
没错
That's right.
去年 我套上裙子
Last year, I slapped on a dress,
就在这个酒吧里转了转
took a few laps around this very bar,
然后我就拿到了
and I got this:
一个叫斯蒂芬妮・麦克罗根妞儿的电话号码
the phone number of one Stephanie McColgan.
就在那晚 我脱下我的裤袜
Later that night, I took off my pantyhose,
接着在她的小裤裤里...留下我的痕迹
and gave her panties... my hose.
没错 泰德
That's right, Ted.
哥已经领先500点了
I am 500 points ahead.
除非你能穿着裙子拿到一个女生的电话号码
Until you can get a girl's digits
否则我们永远不会打平的
while wearing a dress, you and I will never be even.
你知道吗 公寓管理员可能正等着我
You know what? The super's probably waiting for me,
而且我刚想起来 我还有一把备用钥匙
and I just remembered there's a spare key
-藏在脚垫下面 晚安了 -等等 等等
under the doormat, so good night. Wait, wait.
-泰德你别走啊 -巴尼 我要走了
Ted, don't go. Barney, I am leaving.
恐怕今晚还是将要淡出记忆
I'm afraid this is just one of those nights
的平凡一夜
we're probably going to forget.
我不这么想 哥们 你看
I don't think so, dude. Look.
如果你在关注我们的话
If you're just joining us, the World Wide News
环球新闻台的天空之眼直升机在曼哈顿上空失控
Eye in the Sky traffic chopper is out of control over Manhattan
而此直升机正由本台的罗宾・舍巴斯基驾驶
and being piloted by our own Robin Scherbatsky.
结局恐怕不妙
This probably won't end well.
孩子们  纽约时不时会有那样一个时刻
Kids, every now and then, New York has a moment
每一个市民都关注着同一件事情
when every eye in the city is watching the same thing.
这就是那样的时刻
This was one of those moments.
我们都屏气凝神关注着
We all watched breathlessly as the pilot on the ground
罗宾听从地面上驾驶员的指示 克服重重困难
told her what to do, and against all odds,
把那架直升机降落在地面上
your Aunt Robin landed that helicopter.
我成功了
I did it.
I did it!
飞行员也同时获救 不久痊愈
The pilot survived and made a full recovery.
至于罗宾
And Robin?
同志们 那是罗宾・舍巴斯基
It's Robin Scherbatsky, everybody!
谢谢大家
Thank you so much.
哦 行了
Oh, okay...
罗宾出名了
Robin got famous.
在之后的几天里 她...
In the next few days, she would...
见了市长
meet the mayor,
上了莱特曼的节目
go on Letterman
甚至一种熟食三明治都以她的名字命名
and even have a deli sandwich named after her.
可更重要的是 在那天晚上
But most importantly, that night,
几乎所有她认识的人
she got a call, text or e-mail
都给她打了电话 发了短信或是写了邮件
from almost everyone she'd ever met.
嗨 马修
Hey, Marshall.
嗨 莉莉
Hey, Lil.
嘿 巴尼
Hey, Barney.
是 我知道你跟一脱衣舞女在谈恋爱
Yes, I know you're dating a stripper.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
嗨 爸爸
Hey, Dad.
为你的小女儿感到自豪吗
You proud of your little girl?
好吧 我继续努力
Okay, I'll keep trying.
宝贝 我知道你为什么
Babe, I think I know why you had
-做春梦梦见兰吉了 -为什么
that sex dream about Ranjit. Why?
你想
Think about it.
他说起他孩子的那种方式
The way he talks about his kids.
他是个好爸爸
He's a wonderful father.
他就跟蓝爸爸 比尔・克劳斯比
Just like Papa Smurf, Bill Cosby...
我们的国父乔治・华盛顿一样
George Washington, the father of our country.
你是被那些伟大的父亲所吸引
You're attracted to great dads.
这就是为什么你爱我
And that's why you love me.
因为我会成为有史以来最伟大的爸爸
Because I'm going to be the greatest dad ever.
是的 就是那样
Sure, that must be it.
莉莉决定不告诉马修
Lily decided not to tell Marshall
那些关于弗兰肯斯坦和
about her dream involving Frankenstein
美女与野兽中茶杯的梦
and the tea cup from Beauty and the Beast.
她想把那些梦留给自己
That one was just for her.
好吧 巴尼 我要走了
Okay, Barney, I got to go.
啥
What?
今晚我们见证了
In the middle of
你穿着睡衣被锁在门外
"The Night You Got Locked Out in Your Pajamas
罗宾成功降落了一架直升机
"And Robin Landed a Freaking Helicopter
和我们还有时间重组创世纪乐团
and There's Still Time to Reunite Genesis?"
兄弟 你的愿望达成了
Dude, you got your wish.
这的确是我们毕生难忘的夜晚
It's a night we'll always remember.
我们为嘛就不能回家呢
Why can't we just go home?
-我不能回家 泰德 -为什么
I can't go home, Ted. Why not?
因为...跟我谈恋爱的是个脱衣舞女
Because... I'm dating a stripper.
是 我看到你在公交车上做的广告了
Yes, I've seen your bus ad.
我明白
I get it.
不 你不懂
No, you don't.
每晚 从晚上9点到凌晨四点
Every night, between 9:00 p.M. And 4:00 a.M.,
我备受煎熬 度日如年
I'm in hell.
我满脑子想的都是奎恩在做什么
All I can think about is what Quinn is doing
她在哪儿做和她在谁身上做
and where she is doing it and who she is doing it on.
如果我不做些让自己分心的事情……
If I don't do something to take my mind off of it...
泰德 你能心安理得的在家里坐着真是太幸运了
You're lucky that you can just go sit around the house, Ted.
我没有那个选择
I don't have that option.
哇哦
Wow.
你爱着那个姑娘
You're in love with this girl.
我真的爱她 泰德
I really am, Ted.
可是
I mean...
她是个脱衣舞女
she's a stripper.
晚些时候
Later that night...
我知道我们现在在冷战中
I know we're not talking right now...
但是我想让你知道
but I just want you to know
我很高兴你没事
I'm glad you're okay
第二天晚上
The next night,
我只想好好在家呆着
all I wanted to do was enjoy a night at home.
但是 有件事我必须去做
But there was something I had to do.
挺不容易的
It wasn't easy,
但感谢上帝 在反复尝试了一晚上之后...
but by God, after a long night of trying...
好吧
Okay.
现在我们平了
Now we're even.
500点
500 points.
赢了
Scoreboard.
这不仅仅是一个
More than a legendary night
我们会永远铭记的传奇之夜
we'd remember forever,
同时巴尼叔叔也需要一个兄弟来帮助他忘记
Uncle Barney needed a bro to help him forget.
在这个故事里 还是一裙装兄弟
In this case, a bro in a dress.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
你喷香水了
Are you wearing perfume?
细部商店专卖男士用品
是中性香味 细部商店买的
It's a unisex fragrance. It was in Details.
-真不错 -就是香水
It's nice. It's perfume.